binarybrokerz.com 2016-11-14

# Privacy Policy - Binary Brokerz

Binary Brokerz does its utmost to ensure the privacy, confidentiality and security of its clients are preserved both throughout their interaction with the company and afterwards, to the fullest extent achievable by the company. By opening a trading account with the Company, the client hereby gives its consent to such collection, processing, storage and use of personal information by the Company as it is provided below.

In order to receive further information, or to open a trading account with Binary Brokerz, the clients must first complete and submit the online application form with the required documents attached. They are requested to give necessary information when filling out the online application form, in order to enable the company to evaluate their application and comply with Laws and Regulations governing the provision of financial services. This information is also used to contact them regarding their online trading account. When clients register with Binary Brokerz they acknowledge their willingness to share with the company certain private information which we also use for the purpose of confirming the client’s identity and ensuring the security of their deposits and trading account. This information is collected in line with our stringent verification procedures which are used to deter international money laundering operations and to ensure the security and safety of our customer’s trading activity throughout.

This Agreement is executed between you (hereinafter “the Client”) and the DSML Ltd, 5 Harbour Exchange Square, London, E14 9GE, UK (hereinafter “the Company”).

Our clients undertake to supply us with true, updated and accurate information about their identity. Furthermore they are required to state categorically that they are registering and trading on their own behalf and are not seeking at any time to act any manner which could be considered fraudulent nor are they seeking to impersonate any other individuals for any purposes whatsoever.

Binary Brokerz’s data collection procedures include the collection of client’s freely disclosed information as shared with the company, in addition to the placement of *cookies for the purposes of gathering data about the manner in which client’s interact with the Binary Brokerz website. The Company may share information with affiliates/business partners in the event such information is reasonably required by such affiliate in order to provide the products or services to its clients. These tools for gathering client’s information are employed for the purpose of ensuring the customer’s own security and all data collected by the company is shared only with individuals within the company (and/or the company’s affiliates and/or the company’s business partners) who are involved with the verification of customer account information for the express purpose of ensuring the customer’s confidentiality and security.

*Cookies: A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Binary Brokerz uses cookies on this website. Binary Brokerz do link the information it stores in cookies to any personally identifiable information the client submits while on its site. Binary Brokerz use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie does expire when the client closes its browser. A persistent cookie remains on the client’s hard drive for an extended period of time. To remove persistent cookies, follow the directions provided in the Internet browser’s “help” file.

Binary Brokerz will never disclose any private or otherwise confidential information in regards to our clients and former clients to third parties without the express, written consent of our clients, except in such specific cases in which disclosure is a requirement under law, or is otherwise necessary in order to perform verification analysis on the client’s identity for the purposes of safeguarding their account and securing their personal information. Binary Brokerz also reserve the right to disclose the client’s personal information when it believes that disclosure is necessary to protect the client’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the company’s site. Binary Brokerz will not be liable for any unlawful or unauthorized use of the client’s personal information resulting from cookies on the company’s website that Binary Brokerz does not have access to or control over.

By registering with Binary Brokerz and through the voluntary interaction they undertake with Binary Brokerz products and services the clients confirm and agree that they consent to the use of all or part of the information they provide concerning their Binary Brokerz trading account, the transactions they undertake through it and the interactions which they perform with the company on behalf of the company. All interactions the customer undertakes with the company will be stored by the company for the purposes of record and as such may be employed by the company in such cases that disputes arise between clients and the company.

Binary Brokerz does its utmost to ensure the confidentiality of its clients personal information including the implementation of data protection procedures designed to ensure client confidentiality. Binary Brokerz ensures that its data protection policy is regularly updated in order to ensure that client’s confidential information is continually safeguarded.

From time to time Binary Brokerz may contact clients whether by phone or email for the purpose of offering them further information about Binary Brokerz binary options trading or financial market trading. In addition the company may, on occasion, seek to contact clients, whether by phone or by email, for the purpose of informing them of unique promotional offerings provided by Binary Brokerz for the client. Clients consent to the receipt of such contact when they consent to our terms and conditions of use when registering with Binary Brokerz. Any person wishing to opt out of further contact with Binary Brokerz at any time whatsoever is entitled to do so, simply by contacting the company whether by phone or email and requesting that no further contact on behalf of the company will be made.
